RANMA1/2
I don't care.
From now on, I don't wanna have
anything to do with you anymore!
Akane?
I think she's broken.
Yeah, she's in shock.
You're cruel.
Just the worst.
Who even are you?
I was thinking the same thing.
I thought Saotome was fighting.
Yeah. Where did he go?
Now isn't the time
to nitpick all the little details.
I'm more worried about Akane.
It's a relief to see
you are free from harm.
Yeah. No damage at all
if we ignore that chunk of hair.
All right, Akane. You can hit me.
Yes. Me too.
- Huh?
- You don't have to hold back.
Do whatever you need to feel better.
She doesn't hide how she feels.
Yeah.
WHO SAYS YOU'RE CUTE
That hurts.
I must have twisted my ankle
when I tripped.
I'm pretty close to the clinic.
I should go.
Aw, she's really upset.
That should do it, Akane.
Take care of yourself.
'Kay, Dr. Tofu. I'll see you later.
Oh, Akane.
Oh! Hey there, big sis.
OSTEOPATHIC CLINIC
Were you in another fight today?
Thank you for taking care of her,
Dr. Tofu. We appreciate it.
Oh! I...
Sure. Well, uh...
You know...
Doctor?
Akane, you've become
quite the little tomboy.
Maybe I should grow my hair long.
Then I could be more like Kasumi.
Huh?
Uh, hello.
You expected me to be crying about this?
Yeah, kinda.
Well, I'm not upset. Leave me alone.
Ah. It's tasty.
Oh, Akane. Did you just get ba--
That's a bit of an overreaction
to a haircut, don't you think?
But what on earth happened to you?
- It was my fault.
- I just figured it was time for a change.
Could you help? I wanna clean it up.
Hmm.
If my worrying about you is
gonna be that annoying,
fine then.
Okay, I gotta go apologize.
Akane!
Oh. So sorry to bother you. Wrong person.
Who are you looking for?
Hmm?
What's wrong? You've got a face.
It is you?
Nice change of pace, right?
Um, I, uh...
Sorry.
Really? Not like you to apologize.
- Hey now.
- It's all right.
Huh?
It's not a big deal. I was wanting
to get a haircut soon anyway.
You okay? You want a piggyback ride?
Stop being nice to me. It's weird.
Oh, Akane.
Good to see you today, Dr. Tofu.
- Wow. You cut your hair short again.
- Yep.
Hmm? Again?
Hmm...
Just looks like a light ankle sprain.
- Doctor.
- Huh?
Do you like it?
Yeah, I think you look very cute.
In fact, I always thought shorter hair
suited you much better.
I figured.
Oh, no.
- Stop crying.
- Did I hurt you?
I'm sorry.
No, I'm sorry.
It's not that. I just need to calm down.
Uh--
What's on your mind?
Can you just be normal?
Hmm?
Well, I feel much better
after letting that out.
Hmm?
Is something wrong?
Ranma?
Huh?
Hmm?
In the clinic, I heard him call you cute.
I'm happy for you.
Uh...
It doesn't really matter. Yet.
Okay, but it might matter
to me a little bit.
Don't worry about the doctor. He's
always had a crush on my older sister.
I'm over it now.
I needed to sort my feelings out first.
Oh. Huh?
I forgot to say earlier, but...
Huh?
That hairstyle looks good on you.
Why are you giving me that look?
Are you feeling okay?
You don't have to make it weird!
I'm okay, really.
Don't worry about cheering me up.
That wasn't what I was doing!
You aren't cute enough
for that compliment in the first place!
Yeah? I never claimed to be cute anyway.
Just listen!
What I'm trying to say is I love you w--
No. I mean...
I guess you don't care what I like.
So I'll just be quiet.
- Ranma.
- Huh?
I'm glad to hear it.
So thanks.
I mean it. I'm happy.
Whoa. Hang on.
Could she actually be...
...kinda cute?
You're open.
Huh?
What the hell was that?
I got you good.
Does that make you feel
a little less guilty now?
- I knew you weren't cute!
- I don't care.
Just you wait, Ranma.
Our duel was left unsettled.
But I'll storm the Tendo Dojo,
and finally put an end to
this violent battle between us.
ANYTHING GOES
MARTIAL ARTS TENDO DOJO
The Tendo Dojo. This must be it.
Wake up, Ranma.
Fight me.
Ranma.
Wake up now!
Mmm.
Enough, Ranma!
- Open your damn eyes!
- Huh?
QUIET!
What the hell, man?
What do you want this late at night?
That's enough out of you.
Revenge comes at any hour
of the day or night!
This is so ridiculous.
I still don't know what I did
to set off this grudge.
Before I deliver you to hell,
I'll share one more thing.
Once I came to the realization that you
ran away from our duel,
I chased you all the way to China!
Really?
So then, you went to Jusenkyo?
So you transform in cold water too?
Enough!
The two of us have nothing more
to discuss.
It's so noisy outside.
Hmm?
- Akane.
- Huh?
Are you up?
Is that you, Kasumi?
You don't think it's a burglar, do you?
I hope not.
Hmm?
I told you it was a burglar.
He's got a sack of things he's stolen.
I'm gonna go beat him up.
- No, don't. You'll get hurt.
- Yeah, but...
Use this.
Huh?
Ryoga.
Ryoga?
That's a relief.
So it was just a friend of Ranma's, then.
Hmm?
Yeah, it's just like I thought.
ILLEGAL DUMPING PROHIBITED
RESPECT THE NEIGHBORHOOD
Ryoga?
I can't believe they were making
all that noise in the middle of the night.
Someone's in here.
Who's there? Show yourself now.
Where'd you come from, little guy?
You're okay.
Come here, you don't have to be scared.
Whoa, you're so wet.
I guess you must have gotten lost
out in the rain?
Aw.
You got a lump here.
I gotta tell you, Ryoga.
I understand how you feel.
But can you stop attacking me
at these weird hours.
I already feel out of place because
this isn't my house.
Ranma, why did you bring that dog inside?
I dunno. I could ask you the same thing.
Why'd you bring in this random pig?
What's got you so upset?
Be a good little piggy.
Let's get some medicine for your head.
What's up with this guy?
Just look at him blush.
Look at him what?
He's a real perv, huh?
Oh, it's a boy.
Oh, yeah. You're right.
So, uh, Ranma, what's with the dog?
Trust me, Ryoga.
I'll take your secret to my grave.
Oh, yeah.
I think that's Yamada's dog, Beth.
Huh?
Uh.
Yeah, this is her. Hi, Beth.
Just look away for a sec.
- What the...
- What are you doing?
I knew this was stupid.
Where are you off to now?
The bath. I ended up getting soaked
because Ryoga chased me in the rain.
Huh?
Take the piggy and warm him up too.
Take a bath with a pig?
Ugh, man.
So, if that wasn't Ryoga,
then where exactly did he run off to?
Hey, man. You're gonna have to stay still.
Okay, one bath coming right up!
Hmm?
Ryoga, so you're a little piggy?
- I will never forgive you.
- Wait, wait, wait!
Okay, so you really went to Jusenkyo.
I did.
While chasing you, I lost myself
within the boundless expanse of China.
The days passed relentlessly.
Damn it.
That bastard Ranma.
Can't believe
he had the nerve to stand me up.
And on that fateful day...
Huh?
Get back here!
There was a strange girl who knocked me
into the spring under the cliff.
And then, my body changed...
From that day on,
the horrors I lived were never ending.
Well done, sir.
This piggy looks especially delicious.
Very good job indeed.
I'll go cook it up right away.
I know of a pool called
Spring Drowned Black Piglet
that exists in Jusenkyo.
A tragic legend
of its origination was that,
a little black piglet drowned
in it over 1,200 years ago.
Ever since that day
the waters were cursed.
Everyone unfortunate enough to fall into
it gets turned into a little black piggy.
Wait a second.
Maybe this tiny fella was a human who fell
into the Spring of Drowned Black Piglet.
Just wanted to have a bit
of a laugh before dinner.
- Hot! Ow, hot! Ow! Hot!
- Oh, so he was a human.
We'll have to eat something else.
My body turned into an abomination.
And then I was almost devoured.
None of this would have happened
if you showed up to fight!
Hey, wait a second.
I thought you were saying
it was some random girl that made you
fall into the spring.
So what if I did?
Then it makes no freakin' sense
for you to hold a grudge against me.
You should be blaming
that panda and the girl... Oh.
Hmm?
PARDON ME!
A panda.
Okay. I get it now. The girl I saw...
Damn you to hell, Ranma!
I'm going to murder you!
Hey!
Let's try and cool off for now.
We can talk about it when you calm down.
What do you say, Ryoga?
Huh?
What the heck are they doing in there?
Get back here! I gave you an inch
and you took a mile.
You cut it out.
Why are you doing this to him?
That's not fair!
You can't just use a girl as your shield.
You damn pig. I'm saying we should try
talking about this more lat...
You need to stop.
Are you okay?
What a poor little guy.
Come on. Let's go.
Uh, hey, just where are you
taking him now?
- To cuddle in bed.
- What?
- No.
- Wait a second.
You dunno where that pig has been.
You're a good boy. Let's not cry anymore.
What's the matter?
Suit yourself! Be an idiot for all I care.
Hmm?
I can't believe him.
Why was Ranma acting so riled up?
He's so immature.
What dummy would be jealous of a pig?
It was jealousy, right?
That's just silly.
Hmm?
Huh?
Keep your mouth shut
and I won't have to about showing her
who you really are.
Hmm?
Huh?
Uh, no. I wasn't gonna...
It's not what it looks like.
Ow! Hey, I was just...
It was Ryoga.
What about Ryoga? He's not here.
The only dirty animal here is you!
Oh, yeah, Ranma.
If you want to get laid in the middle
the night, can you be quieter?
Well, in my opinion, it's far too early
for both of you to be doing that.
Glad you're a healthy boy, at least.
You've got it all wrong!
MORE, PLEASE!
Sometimes I don't believe this family.